{
	"games" : [
		{
		    "questions" : [
		        {
		            "question" : "Who is the president of the USA?",
		            "content" : [
		                "Donald Duck",
		                "Jack Sparrow",
		                "Donald Trump",
		                "Kim Kardashian"
		            ],
								"correct" : [2],
								"money": 500
		        },
		        {
		            "question" : "What company logo contains red?",
		            "content" : [
		                "Ducati",
		                "Pepsi",
		                "Apple",
		                "Vodafone"
		            ],
								"correct" : [0, 3],
								"money": 1000
		        },
		        {
		            "question" : "Which material is most dense?",
		            "content" : [
		                "Silver",
		                "Styrofoam",
		                "Butter",
		                "Gold"
		            ],
								"correct" : [3],
								"money": 2000
		        },
		        {
		            "question" : "Which state in the United States is largest by area?",
		            "content" : [
		                "Alaska",
		                "California",
		                "Texas",
		                "Hawaii"
		            ],
								"correct" : [0],
								"money": 4000
		        },
		        {
		            "question" : "Who wrote 4 seasons?",
		            "content" : [
		                "Mozart",
		                "Vivaldi",
		                "Bach",
		                "Chaikovsky"
		            ],
								"correct" : [1],
								"money": 8000
		        },
				{
						"correct" : [3],
						"money": 16000,
				    "question": "Galileo was an Italian astronomer who:",
						"content": [
				        "developed the telescope",
				        "discovered four satellites of Jupiter",
				        "discovered that the movement of pendulum produces a regular time measurement",
				        "All of the above"
				    ]
				},
				{
						"correct" : [2],
						"money": 32000,
				    "question": "When is Ukrainian Independence Day?",
						"content": [
				        "21 Aug",
				        "27 Aug",
				        "24 Aug",
				        "14 Aug"
				    ]
				},
				{
						"correct" : [1],
						"money": 64000,
				    "question": "How many countries are EU Members?",
				    "content": [
				        "18",
				        "28",
				        "22"
				    ]
				},
				{
						"correct" : [3],
						"money": 125000,
				    "question": "The first iPhone was introduced in:",
						"content": [
				        "Sep 6, 2007",
				        "Sep 12, 2007",
				        "Oct 14, 2008",
				        "June 29, 2007"
				    ]
				},
				{
						"correct" : [2],
						"money": 250000,
				    "question": "When is the International Workers' Day?",
						"content": [
				        "15th April",
				        "12th December",
				        "1st May",
				        "1st August"
				    ]
				},
				{
						"correct" : [0, 1, 2, 3],
						"money": 500000,
				    "question": "Select all car models Tesla has annouced:",
						"content": [
				        "S",
				        "3",
				        "X",
				        "Y"
				    ]
				},
				{
						"correct" : [1],
						"money": 1000000,
				    "question": "Instagram was sold for: ",
						"content": [
				        "$18b",
				        "$1b",
				        "$150m",
				        "$500mil"
				    ]
				},
				{
						"correct" : [1],
						"money": 500,
				    "content": [
				        "I want to break free",
				        "Hello darkness",
				        "The show must go on",
				        "We are the champions"
				    ],
				    "question": "What song is not written by Queen?"
				},
				{
						"correct" : [0, 1, 3, 4],
						"money": 500,
				    "content": [
				        "Kyiv",
								"Odessa",
								"Warsaw",
								"Lviv",
								"Kharkiv"
							],
				    "question": "Select all Ukrainian cities:"
				}
				],
				"currency": "$"
		}
	]
}